(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
雪花ラミィ アイドル衣装
Yukihana Lamy Idol Costume
いぇーい！みんなー！
Yay! Everyone!
こんらみー！
Kon-Lamy!
ホロライブ5期生、雪花ラミィでーす！こんらみー！
I'm Yukihana Lamy, Hololive 5th Gen! Kon-Lamy!
いや、おまるん、よかったねー！
Wow, Omarun (Polka) was great!
すごい可愛かった。もう次はラミィがね、
She was so cute. Now it's Lamy's turn...
みんなにお披露目する感じになるので、緊張しておりますが、
...to reveal it to everyone, so I'm really nervous, but...
今日は #ねぽらぼアイドル衣装 でみんな、いっぱいつぶやいてね！
Please tweet a lot today with #NePoLaBoIdolCostume!
ということで、ラミィも、この後、
So, after this, Lamy is also...
アイドル衣装に着替えて、1曲、みんなに披露したいと思っております！
...going to change into my idol costume and perform a song for you!
あー緊張するー！
Ah, I'm so nervous!
それでは！お着替えー！
Well then! Time to change!
さらん！
Ta-da!
じゃーん！
Bam!
それでは、いくぞー！
Now, here we go!
あわいホイップしたケーキのような街は
The town, like a lightly whipped cake,
すき！ゆき！マジマジマジック！
Is Love! Snow! Real, Real Magic!
空がくれるコンフェッティは
The confetti given by the sky
冬のベスタ　いわば天使の羽よ　わぁ！
Is Winter's Vesta, or rather, angel's wings! Whoa!
好き！雪！本気マジック！ 作詞・作曲：Mitchie M
Suki! Yuki! Honki Magic! / Lyrics & Composition: Mitchie M
白銀の国へ　出かけるの Go-Go-Go
Setting off to the silver land, Go-Go-Go
雪の馬車が　街を駆け　Chu-Chu-Chu
A snow carriage runs through the town, Chu-Chu-Chu
絵本みたいな景色を　君に見せてあげるから
I'll show you a scene just like a picture book
願い込めて　呪文さぁ　唱えて (My Mai!)
So put your wishes into it and chant the spell (My Mai!)
A B C D Do-Do Si-Si La-La Si-Si
マジカル　ミラクル　クルッポ！
Magical Miracle Kuruppo!
あわいホイップしたケーキのような街は
The town, like a lightly whipped cake,
すき！ゆき！マジマジマジック！
Is Love! Snow! Real, Real Magic!
空がくれるコンフェッティは
The confetti given by the sky
冬のベスタ　いわば天使の羽よ
Is Winter's Vesta, or rather, angel's wings
ライトアップしたオーロラ色の街は
The aurora-colored town lit up
すき！ゆき！マジマジマジック！
Is Love! Snow! Real, Real Magic!
子供でいられるな　ドリームランド
Is a dreamland where you can stay a child
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to Yukihana Lamy!
ずっと冷たい　季節が　Love-Love-Love
The cold season will always be Love-Love-Love
アイス魔法も　解けないように　Hyu-Hyu-Hyu
So that the ice magic won't melt, Hyu-Hyu-Hyu
ずっとこのままじゃダメなの？ やっぱりドキドキしたいな
Is it no good to stay like this forever? I still want my heart to throb
未来　求め　呪文今　唱えて (Now!)
Seeking the future, chant the spell now (Now!)
1 2 3 4 水・金・地・火・木・土・天・海
1 2 3 4 Mercury, Venus, Earth, Mars, Jupiter, Saturn, Uranus, Neptune
マジカル　ミラクル　クルッポ！
Magical Miracle Kuruppo!
あわほっぷしたウサギのような気分
Feeling like a bubbly rabbit
すき！ゆき！マジマジマジック！
Love! Snow! Real, Real Magic!
大地がくれるケーキ皿は
The cake plate the earth gives us
思い通り遊んでいけるよ
Lets us play however we want
まぶしい白に染まるハート　君に
A heart dyed in dazzling white, for you
すき！ゆき！マジマジマジック！
Love! Snow! Real, Real Magic!
大人のフリなんて　いいじゃん！
Pretending to be an adult is fine!
I'm the Lamy-lamy-tan!
Thank you and welcome-dan!
This is Yukihana Lamy-no!
This is Yukihana Lamy's!
なまらファンタスティック！
Namara fantastic!
The snow is ミシカル！
The snow is mythical!
エクセレント・マジカル！
Excellent magical!
I'll take you for it my Lamy! Oh-oh-oh!
今日の寒さも忘れるように
So that you'll forget today's coldness
悩みだって　涙だって　凍らせて　消せる魔法よ　わぁ！
Troubles and tears, this magic will freeze and erase them! Whoa!
A B C D Do-Do Si-Si La-La Si-Si
マジカル　ミラクル　クルッポ！
Magical Miracle Kuruppo!
あわいホイップしたケーキのような街は
The town, like a lightly whipped cake,
すき！ゆき！マジマジマジック！
Is Love! Snow! Real, Real Magic!
空がくれるコンフェッティは
The confetti given by the sky
冬のベスタ　いわば天使の羽よ
Is Winter's Vesta, or rather, angel's wings
ライトアップしたオーロラ色の街は
The aurora-colored town lit up
すき！ゆき！マジマジマジック！
Is Love! Snow! Real, Real Magic!
子供でいられるな　ドリームランド
Is a dreamland where you can stay a child
いぇーい！
Yay!
あらー見たって！天才！
Oh, look at that! Genius!
優勝！
Victory!
みんな、きてたの？
Everyone, were you here?
きたよー！
I'm here!
We're here!
ということで、マリン先輩と...
So, Marine-senpai and...
一人一人ちょっと名前言ってもらおうかな。
I'll have each of you say your names one by one.
お、お、誰が先行く？
Oh, oh, who goes first?
あーい、マリンと！
Ah-hoy, with Marine and!
まっする、ノエルこ、
Muscle, Noel-ko,
迷うな迷うな、ちょっと迷っちゃった、やばい、遠慮しちゃった。
Don't hesitate, I hesitated a bit, oh no, I was too reserved.
ゆび！こうじだよ！
Finger! It's Koji!
略してきたな。
You shortened it.
なんかすごいねまとまりないな。
Somehow there's no unity at all.
ありがとう来てくれて。
Thank you for coming.
ラミィちゃーん！どれ、何見せてみなさいよ。
Lamy-chan! Well, let's see what you've got.
ほらー、じっくり、じっくり見ていく、じっくり。
See, look closely, look closely, closely.
上から順番にファッションコーデいこうか。
Let's go through the fashion coordinate from the top.
帽子かわいい、それ。
That hat is cute.
あ、そう、帽子ね、これ、ほら。
Oh, right, the hat, this one, see.
おー、オシャレ。可愛い。
Oh, stylish. Cute.
ね、普段からね、帽子かぶってるからね。
Right, because you always wear a hat, don't you?
あ、そうそうそう、普段からね、白い帽子被ってるから、
Ah, yes yes yes, since I always wear a white hat,
これはアイドル衣装バージョンの帽子。
this is the idol costume version of the hat.
めっちゃいい。
That's really good.
ほら、もうちょい下に降りて顔見ようかな。
Hey, let's go a bit lower and see your face.
あ、顔顔、はい、うわー、可愛い、1000万点！
Ah, face face, yes, wow, cute, 10 million points!
もうちょっと下に降りようかな。下、下、に。
Let's go a bit lower. Down, down, to...
おお、おお、デカい、これですよ。
Oh, oh, big, this is it.
ちょっと、ちょっとジャンプしてごらん。
Just, try jumping for a bit.
なんでよ！
Why?!
ん、ちょっとできないのかな？
Hm, can't you do it?
あ、なんか思ったより硬いな。
Ah, it's firmer than I thought.
カチカチや、ちょっとでも踊るからね、揺れないようにしてもらって。
It's rock solid, but I'll be dancing, so I have them make it not shake.
あ、なるほどね、クーパー靭帯をね、大事にしている。
Ah, I see, you're taking care of your Cooper's ligaments.
さすがアイドルや。
As expected of an idol.
じゃあちょっと下降りる？後ろも見たいね。
Then shall we go down a bit? We want to see the back too.
お、なんか、後ろ側も見たいよね。
Oh, something, we want to see the back side too.
あ、あ、リボン！ピンクいいな、差し色！
Ah, ah, the ribbon! Pink is nice, as an accent color!
ほら、映えてるね、リボンをピンクにしてもらいました。
See, it stands out, I had them make the ribbon pink.
お、めっちゃいいじゃん。ヨキヨキ、可愛い。
Oh, that's really good. Nice nice, cute.
色もいい、この水色もいい。
And the color is good, this light blue is good too.
ありがとう。
Thank you.
今日はちょっと撮影会みたいなことしようかなと思うんだけど。
Today I'm thinking of doing something like a photo session.
一人ずつ、なんかこれをしてほしいみたいなポーズがあればやろうかなと思うんだけど、
I'm thinking of doing poses that each of you might want me to do,
なんかあります？
is there anything?
誰が先行く？どうする？いいよ、誰でもいいよ。
Who goes first? What should we do? It's okay, anyone is fine.
はい、はい、はい、じゃあ船長行きます。
Yes, yes, yes, then the Captain will go.
せっかくアイドル衣装だからちょっとアイドル然としたポーズが見たいわけ。
Since it's an idol costume after all, I want to see a pose that's truly idol-like.
アイドル然としたポーズ。
A truly idol-like pose.
ポーズ、ピタッと止まってるやつじゃなくてちょっと動いてからの、みたいのが見たいから。
Not a pose where you're just perfectly still, I want to see something after a bit of movement.
おい、ハードルを上げるな。
Hey, don't raise the bar.
軽くステップ踏んで、くるっと回って、キメみたいなのが見たい。
Take a few light steps, spin around, and then a "kime" pose, that's what I want to see.
あ、いいよ。
Ah, okay.
ある、いくよ。はい、どうぞ。
Here we go. Yes, go ahead.
振りが雑だなぁ、えーと...
The setup is so rough, let's see...
えーと、どうしようかな。
Hmm, what should I do.
いいよ, 好きなステップ。
It's okay, whatever steps you like.
じゃあ、アイドルステップから、の。
Then, from an idol step, to...
可愛い、いいじゃん！スクショタイム！優勝！
Cute, nice! Screenshot time! Victory!
いや、めちゃくちゃ可愛い。
No, it's incredibly cute.
ありがとう。
Thank you.
次はね、膝ついて、後ろ向いて膝ついて。
Next is, kneel down, turn around and kneel down.
膝ついて、後ろ向いて膝つく。
Kneel down, turn around and kneel down.
で、こう, こっちを振り返って。
And then, like this, look back this way.
で、あら、可愛い、そうそうそう、できるじゃんか。
And, oh, cute, yes yes yes, you can do it.
なー、できるじゃんか。プロデューサー。
See, you can do it. Producer.
カメラ上から、あ、いい、いい、いい、いやー。
Camera from above, ah, good, good, good, wow.
もっと表情見せてごらん、表情。はい、困った顔。
Show us more of your expression, your expression. Yes, a troubled face.
あら、困っちゃったね。めっちゃいいじゃん。困ってんの？
Oh, you're troubled, aren't you. That's really good. Are you troubled?
えー、次、団長、団長。
Um, next, Danchou, Danchou.
じゃあ団長はね、後ろから走ってきて、某Ｑ、Ｑジャンプをしてほしいなと思って。
Then for Danchou, run from the back, and I want you to do that certain Q, Q jump.
Ｑ、Ｑジャンプ。なるほど、青春。
Q, Q jump. I see, youth.
フレンドだからね、一人Ｑジャンプ。思い切り、思い切り。
Because we're friends, a solo Q jump. With all your might, all your might.
はい！
Yes!
可愛い、可愛い。
Cute, cute.
もっと助走つけて思い切り、行くよ、せーの。
More of a running start with all your might, here we go, one, two...
おー！
Oh!
かわいい！
So cute!
いいね！
Nice!
なにげにこの足元の靴下もね、かわいいね、めちゃくちゃ。
By the way, these socks on my feet are also really, really cute.
めちゃかわいい！そうなのよ！
Super cute! They really are!
これあれじゃん！お花の…あの、髪飾りの柄だ。
Wait, look at this! It's the flower... the same pattern as my hair ornament.
そうそうそうそう！
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
リボンもなんか付いてるんだけど。
There's also a ribbon attached to it.
どうしたの？取れたの？
What happened? Did it come off?
あ、そう、靴下に持ってきたんだよ、靴下に。ぷいってね。
Ah, right, I moved it down to the socks. Just like that.
今回は…今回は、このアイドル衣装だから、ちょっとシンプルめにね。
This time... since it's an idol outfit, I made it a bit on the simpler side.
あのね、帽子を引き立たせるために、そうしました。
You see, I did that to make the hat stand out.
おー！めちゃいいじゃん！凝ってるよ！
Ooh! That's great! It's so stylish!
みんな、どこが一番好き？
What part do you all like best?
どこ？えー…
Which part? Hmm...
うーん、ラミィたんのお顔！
Umm, Lamy-tan's face!
あー、やめてー！
Aah, stop it!
何着ててもかわいいよ！
You're cute no matter what you wear!
ありがとう！もももも…
Thank you! *Muttering happily*
やめてくれる？顔、顔がすごく…
Can you stop? Your face, your face is just...
（笑い声）
(Laughter)
顔ね。あ、ねねちゃんは？
My face, huh. Ah, what about Nene-chan?
団長は…やっぱり足元のその、やっぱりストッキングじゃなくて、靴下、ソックス！
As for me... I really like the feet, not the stockings, but the socks!
やっぱりお花があるのがめちゃめちゃかわいいなと思って。
I thought the flowers on them were really, really cute.
ありがとう！細いし、足。
Thank you! And your legs are so thin.
え、なんかさ、それ、ねねちゃんもしかして自分が雪の柄奪っちゃったからその贖罪の…
Wait, maybe Nene-chan gave you those for atonement since she stole the snow pattern...?
ば、バレちゃった？めちゃめちゃたくさん雪の柄…
I'm b-busted? I do have a lot of snow patterns...
そんなお揃い感はあるよね、ねねちゃんパイと。
There's definitely a matching feel there with Nene-chan.
そうだね、おそろち、おそろち。
That's right, matching, matching.
並びたいなー。
I want to stand next to you.
え、なんかもう一個、うちら三人からポーズ指定していいかな？
Um, can the three of us specify one more pose for you?
え、どうする？どういう感じで？なんかみんな…
Eh, what should I do? In what way? Everyone...
じゃ、スロットで行こう、スロットで。
Then let's go with a 'slot', a slot.
スロット？どういうこと？
Slot? What do you mean?
ぽるこにが顔の角度やって…
Pol-koni will decide the face angle...
ノエルちゃんが…何だっけ？上半身やって…
Noel-chan will... what was it? Do the upper body...
マリンが下半身を。
And Marine will do the lower body.
上半身、オッケーオッケー。
Upper body, okay, okay.
お、下半身のマリンね。任せろ！下半身のことなら。
Oh, Marine for the lower body. Leave it to me! I'm the expert on lower bodies.
どこからやる？そしたら。
Where should we start then?
え、待って、上から順じゃないの？こういうの。
Wait, shouldn't we go from the top down? For these things.
ぽちゃま角度やるよ。ぽるこに先輩から。
I'll do the face angle. Starting from Pol-koni-senpai.
うんっとね、左にちょっと傾けて。
Umm, tilt your head a little to the left.
左にちょっと…オッケー。
A little to the left... Okay.
いいね！それだけ？
Nice! Is that all?
え、表情、表情の指定と。
Um, and specifying the expression, the expression.
表情？じゃあ、こに困った顔好きだから困った顔がいいな。
Expression? Well, since I love troubled faces, a troubled face would be good.
照れてるような感じの。あ、あらららら！女優、女優！いいよいいよ！
Like you're blushing. Oh, my, my! An actress, a real actress! Good, good!
上半身！やっぱり団長マッスルポーズが好きだからマッスルじゃない？
Upper body! Since I love muscle poses, it's gotta be muscles, right?
スロット！嘘でしょ？
Slot! You're kidding, right?
ガショーン！いいねいいね！
*Clank!* Nice, nice!
ちょっと待って！バランス悪いぞ！
Wait a minute! The balance is terrible!
いやでもね、下半身決めてくれる。
No, but really, let me decide the lower body.
船長はやっぱり、女の子はね、膝から崩れ落ちてるのがいいと思う。
I think for girls, collapsing to their knees is the best.
膝から崩れ落ちて！はい、崩れ落ちて、ラミィたん。
Collapse to your knees! Come on, collapse, Lamy-tan.
どういうことなの？もうちょっと足開こうか？
What do you mean? Should I spread my legs more?
やだよ！開かないで！
No! Don't spread them!
もう！かわいくないじゃん！やだちょっと、船長！
Geez! That's not cute at all! Stop it, Senchou!
（笑い声）
(Laughter)
上半身戦犯だよこれ！これはやっぱりノエル先輩が戦犯だわ。
The upper body is the culprit here! This is definitely Noel-senpai's fault.
やっちゃったやっちゃった。
I did it, I did it.
足元…え、もう終わり？終わり？
The feet... eh, is it over already? Is it over?
もしかしてお時間なので。
Because it's probably time.
あ、そうなの？みんなありがとうね！
Ah, is that so? Thank you everyone!
ありがとう！かわいかったよ、ラミィたん！ありがとう！
Thank you! You were so cute, Lamy-tan! Thank you!
バイバイ！バイバイ！またねー！
Bye bye! Bye bye! See you later!
ということで、皆様ももうそろそろお時間なので、ししろの枠に行きましょう！ゴー！
And so, since it's almost time for everyone, let's head over to Shishiro's stream! Go!
雪花ラミィ アイドル衣装
Yukihana Lamy Idol Costume